fillz.com 2019-03-30

# Fillz | Privacy

Last Updated: December 15th, 2011

Fillz knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. Please note that Fillz is a division of AbeBooks, Inc. ("AbeBooks"). As a part of AbeBooks, Fillz follows the same information practices as AbeBooks, and information we collect is subject to the AbeBooks Privacy Notice.

**By visiting the Fillz site, you are accepting the practices described in the[AbeBooks Privacy Notice](http://www.abebooks.com/docs/Legal/privacyPolicy.shtml "AbeBooks.com Privacy Policy").**

## Privacy Notice Changes

Fillz is a division of AbeBooks, and we have updated the Fillz.com Privacy Notice to be consistent with the AbeBooks.com Privacy Notice. This updated Privacy Notice will apply to personal information you provide after December 15th, 2011 or that we store and use in connection with your transactions after December 15th, 2011.

The policy is now divided into a few main sections, such as personal information we gather, how we share information, third-party advertising, and user choices. Although there are similarities to our past policy, there are some changes.

For example:

  * The updated policy describes the different types of information we gather and how we gather information about you. 
  * The updated policy describes the limited ways we share information about you.
  * The updated policy allows information to be shared among AbeBooks.com's affiliates, including its parent corporation, Amazon.com, Inc. 

These are only a few of the changes to the policy, and this brief summary should not affect your interpretation of it. Please read the [Privacy Notice](http://www.abebooks.com/docs/Legal/privacyPolicy.shtml "AbeBooks.com Privacy Policy") carefully. Your continued use of the Fillz.com website constitutes your acceptance of the updated Privacy Notice.
